"use strict"

const questionStore = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What does CSS stand for?',
        answers: [
            'a) Cascading Style Sheets',
            'b) Color Styling Sheets',
            'c) Cascading Styling Source',
            'd) Color Style Sheet'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'a) Cascading Style Sheets'        
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which ruleset respects width and height of a box-model?',
        answers: [
            'a) box-model: border-size',
            'b) box-model: border-box',
            'c) box-sizing: border-box',
            'd) box-sizing: border-size'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'c) box-sizing: border-box'        
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Which position is set by default?',
        answers: [
            'a) fixed',
            'b) relative',
            'c) default',
            'd) static'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'd) static'        
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Which element cannot have set width and height?',
        answers: [
            'a) span',
            'b) h1',
            'c) div',
            'd) form'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'a) span'        
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Could keyword !important affect CSS rule of higher specificity?',
        answers: [
            'a) yes',
            'b) works only for headings',
            'c) no',
            'd) only within a form'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'a) yes'      
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is viewport?',
        answers: [
            'a) users screen dimensions',
            'b) users screen location',
            'c) users hidden area of a webpage',
            'd) users visible area of a webpage'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'd) users visible area of a webpage'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What keyword helps us target a special state of an element?',
        answers: [
            'a) pseudo-element',
            'b) pseudo-id',
            'c) pseudo-class',
            'd) pseudo-parameter'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'c) pseudo-class'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'We can create responsive layouts using..',
        answers: [
            'a) positioning',
            'b) flex-box',
            'c) floats',
            'd) text-align'
        ],
       correctAnswer: 'b) flex-box'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Progressive enhancement approach refers to...',
        answers: [
            'a) desktop first design',
            'b) mobile design',
            'c) mobile first design',
            'd) desktop design'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'c) mobile first design'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What do margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto do?',
        answers: [
            'a) center a block element',
            'b) center an inline element',
            'c) resize the width of an element',
            'd) stretch the width of an element'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'a) center a block element'
    }
];

